<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abstract on RequestCoin</title>
    <link>http://requestco.in/abstract/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abstract on RequestCoin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 23:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://requestco.in/abstract/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Example</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/abstract/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 22:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/abstract/example/</guid>
      <description>In the not-to-distant future, farmers all around the world could pay Ether into a smart contract that would provide agricultural insurance against hail or drought. Then, throughout the year, as &amp;ldquo;request miners&amp;rdquo; detect these specific weather conditions using multiple APIs and other internet sources, the contract would deterministically pay Ether back to the farmers in need. This incredibly efficient system completely sidesteps an entire field of insurance agents and adjusters, immediately helping the farmers in need without any unnecessary overhead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utility Token</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/abstract/utilitytoken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 21:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/abstract/utilitytoken/</guid>
      <description>The first thing to address in building a decentralized oracle network is the cryptoeconomics of incentivizing miners. To do this we will create a utility token that can be used to purchase the efforts of request miners. Any given channel of data will need a consensus and to drive that consensus, an amount of token will be put up for grabs. As miners reach a consensus on the blockchain they will be rewarded with the token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Off-chain Consensus</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/abstract/offchainconsensus/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/abstract/offchainconsensus/</guid>
      <description>A purely on-chain solution to the decentralized oracle problem faces a big hurdle due to gas prices when reaching a consensus. If every miner has to post results to the blockchain, they will spend way more gas than economically viable. Plus, other miners could simply echo what previous miners posted and earn the token reward without actually making the request. It is at least worth mentioning that it would be a lot cheaper (gas) to simply trigger an on-chain event without storing anything, but an off-chain solution allows for a lot more functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contract Lineage</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/abstract/contractlineage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 19:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/abstract/contractlineage/</guid>
      <description>Writing and deploying a contract on the Ethereum blockchain is relatively easy, but writing and deploying a safe and secure fleet of contracts is extremely difficult. Inevitably, code will need to be upgraded as vulnerabilities are exposed and new functionality is needed.
The best strategy to provide upgradability to contracts is using many different, interconnected contracts that each have a simple job within a larger system. For example, one contract will be used to store requests and another will manipulate them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/abstract/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/abstract/governance/</guid>
      <description>Initially, contracts will be very malleable, freezable, and quickly replaced. But, as the fleet becomes more stable and more secure, a system of token stake will take power and no single account will be able to control the governance of the network.
A governance contract (called Auth for now) powered by a voting democracy will replace the dictatorship of a small group of developers as soon as the network is large enough to keep out the trolls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>