<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Further on RequestCoin</title>
    <link>http://requestco.in/further/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Further on RequestCoin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 19:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://requestco.in/further/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplification</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/further/simplification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/further/simplification/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s good to talk about what we are not trying to accomplish yet.
Privacy: We are not looking at privacy in any way, for now. Everything within the realm of RequestCoin is 100% public. If you spend the token to get the current price of corn on the blockchain, that transaction along with the actual price of corn is available on the blockchain for everyone.
Private APIs: We are assuming that only public data is fair game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Similar Projects</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/further/similarprojects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 03:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/further/similarprojects/</guid>
      <description>There are a handful of extremely interesting projects in this space.
Vitalik Buterin himself wrote about a decentralized oracle all the way back in 2014 he called schellingcoin.
The most similar, but much more advanced is ChainLink. These guys have a tremendous amount of momentum. ChainLink is a complex system of data providers and data proxies that is tightly coupled with financial organizations and big name research organizations. RequestCoin is a very simple, raw, decentralized network of oracles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://requestco.in/further/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 02:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://requestco.in/further/resources/</guid>
      <description>Solidity Docs should probably be your first stop when learning smart contracts.
Consensys has a bunch of resources on their website and github including their Smart Contract Best Practices.
OpenZeppelin has a github that is full of hardened and tested contracts.
Decypher Media is an awesome feed of videos put together by Jordan Leigh
Reddit: r/ethereum r/ethdev</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>